<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Cubie</string>
    <string name="womenInTech">\n\nCommunity investment and decisive career growth from Capital One’s Women in Tech\n
        According to a recent LinkedIn survey, we are starting to see gender parity across many of the top 15 rising job categories. However, some of the hottest new tech roles are not on that list. How we, as women in tech, lead over the next few years will be crucial in bridging the gender gap in these technology fields. To help answer how we can make these changes on both a personal and industry level, I’ve talked to some of my colleagues at Capital One, to create a five-blog series on how to lead as women in tech.\n

        Why integrate work and personal life as women in tech?\n
        In its traditional use, the term “work life balance” compartmentalized work and life, setting them up in opposition to one another. Over the last year, due to COVID-19, there has been a paradigm shift in how we work. Many companies went virtual during the pandemic, with many of us still working from home a year and a half later. For many of us, all lines have blurred between work and personal life. There are no compartments.\n

        The term “work life integration” is about bringing together the synergies between work and life. With this approach, you may find yourself better able to consider all the aspects of your life–work and career, home and family, personal well-being and health, and giving back and connecting with the community–without having to fall back on compartmentalization.\n

        How to integrate work and personal life as women in tech\n
        While this is the last part of my five part blog series, - you can read Parts 1, 2, 3, and 4 here - it certainly isn’t the least important one. I saved this for last since you will need to incorporate these five tips into each and every phase of your career journey, regardless of where you are.</string>

    <string name="womenInTech2">\n1. Practice mindfulness for personal and professional success\n
To have a successful career in tech you don’t need to give up on your family time or hobbies. You don’t need to work 80 hours a week or be under constant stress from an unreasonable workload. Being present in the moment, focusing on one task at a time, and ‘slowing down to speed up things’ are all great ways to enjoy the work you are doing. Taking breaks that fit your schedule and recharging as needed are an important aspect of maintaining a sustainable pace. Here are some tips on how to be more mindful at work that I have found useful in my tech career.\n

A few years ago I was part of a leadership program where we learnt about better integrating work and personal life by putting together all our personal and professional goals in one place. As part of the exercise, I worked through a quiz to check what I had versus what I wanted. At the end of the quiz, I was able to score my success level (meeting my career goals) and my sanity level (able to enjoy my life) on a scale of 1 to 10.

This was intended to highlight where I was meeting my goals, where I was exceeding them, and where I was falling short. Personally, this helped me appreciate the areas I was doing well in and helped me focus on tangible goals I could go after in areas where I was not. And having both personal and professional goals in one place helped relieve the pressure of walking a tightrope between the two. Once I started to view everything in terms of “success and sanity” for my holistic life I found myself enjoying what I was doing, even when it meant juggling different things occasionally.\n</string>

    <string name="rog">\n\nContestants bid in order from left to right and must bid as close as they can to the actual retail price without going over.\n Contestants bid in dollars and not cents as the retail prices are rounded off to the nearest dollar and may not bid the same amount as any player bid previously for that prize. All points are paid through Capital One Wow bucks... Have fun and may the odds ever be in your favor.</string>
</resources>